# Kimberly Champagne

T: (954) 914-4874 E: contact@kimberlychampagne.com Website: kimberlychampagne.com

# **Objective**

To succeed in applying the knowledge and experience gained through studying psychology statistics, and software coding to tackle any task handed to me. To also grow in a stimulating environment that will provide me with opportunities to learn, and make great connections while contributing as much as possible to meet the company's goals.

### **Technical Skills**

- o Programming languages: SAS, R, SQL, SPSS, HTML, CSS, Python, Javascript, Command Line
- o Frameworks and Libraries: React JS, Angular JS, Ionic, Flask
- o API's: Mailgun, Clarifai, GoogleMaps
- o Hardware: Basic Arduino Knowledge, EEG usage and data analysis

#### **Extracurriculars**

- Accepted into Domi Station's Get Started Program (Tallahassee's premier incubator program) for an App project
- Case is an App that utilizes the ionic framework using HTML, CSS, Typescript, Python, Flask, SQL, etc
- ShellMaps.com is a minority-owned business map with crowd funding opportunities. Winner of the Woman in Computer Science(WiCS) x Microsoft challenge at ShellHacks hackathon in Miami, Florida
- o Chosen to present my published research at the Human Computer Interaction Conference in Vancouver, Canada
  - Honors Thesis: Predictors of Mobile Device Usage and Proficiency Among Older Adults

### **Education**

The Honors College at Florida State University, Tallahassee, Florida (Magna Cum Laude)

May 2017

- Full-time undergraduate student studying Psychology and Statistics.
- o Research assistant in numerous labs.
  - Assisted in the Florida Department of Transportation lab at FSU under Dr. Walter Boot and Dr. Neil Charness
  - Volunteered in the KATLAB studying the neural markers of anxiety in children under Dr. Alexandra Meyer.
    - Used an EEG machine on many research participants and conducted EEG analyses.
- Presented data from the Florida Department of Transportation (FDOT) lab at Undergraduate Research Day and Psychology
  Undergraduate Research Day, held yearly and attended by our school president, other administration and professors
- Completed my Statistics minor by pursuing a SAS certificate, which requires 4 courses with the coding program implemented.
- o Political Science Learning coordinator for the Catalyst Club under the Black Student Union at Florida State.
- o GPA: 3.98

The Honors College at Florida International University, Miami, Florida

May 2015

o Full-time sophomore student studying Pre-Med and Psychology in their Honors College program.

Broward College, Pembroke Pines, Florida

May 2014

- Enrolled in their Early Admissions program for high school students.
- o AP Scholar graduating high school with over a year of college completed
- Took 4 AP classes (AP Art History, AP language Arts, AP American History, and AP World History)
- o Graduated top 15% of my class with a 4.5 GPA

# **Experience**

**Evans Economic Consulting Agency** 

May 2017

o Helped clean and organize large data sets for statistical analysis.

- Technical advisor for all IOS (iPhones, iPads, and iPods) devices, as well as their compatibility with customer's computers
- Team MVP numerous times because of outstanding metrics
- Learned about the rich business history of this company, as well as the software and hardware that has been manufactured by them over the years
- o Consistently lead the team in issue resolution time and customer satisfaction
- Consistently met or exceeded expectations during every quarterly performance review
- Given accolades by management in the Student Union employee recognition page emailed to everyone that's a part of the college program
- o Chosen as an extender in the college program after the 1 year internship was over
- o Chosen to extend to a permanent position at Apple, after graduation in May 2017

### Chick-Fil-A Fountains of Miramar, Miramar, Florida

December 2011-August 2013

- Certified trainer responsible for ensuring new hire's understanding of their position and responsibilities in the restaurant.
- Responsible for ensuring my own front of house duties while having to make sure customer service met Chick-Fil-A's outstanding standards.
- o Great preparation for my up coming jobs in the fine dining industry.

#### **Volunteering**

Children's Harbor Foster Home Volunteer through PPCHS T.R.O.O.P Club

August 2010-May 2012

- o Through my High School's T.R.O.O.P club (Teens Reaching Out to Other People), of which I was treasurer, every month we would visit the Children's Harbor foster home in our community
- Over a span of 2 years, we would visit the foster children here, bringing them toys and clothes.
- We would fundraise for goods at our school, so that more people could be involved to bring about a change.
- We would talk to the children who ranged in age from toddler to seventeen, and the connection and understanding our group experienced was priceless.

Abundant Living Ministries Nursery Worker, Pembroke Pines, Florida

September 2009-May 2014

- o At 15, I became a nursery volunteer at the church I grew up in, Abundant Living Ministries.
- o Took charge of the 3-4 year old department, creating weekly Sunday school courses while watching over, feeding, and ensuring the safety of every child there

# References

Dixie Shelton, Apple Manager

• (501) 940-4641

Dr. Walter Boot, Florida Department of Transportation Research Lab Director and personal Honors Thesis director

- 850 644 2040
- boot@psy.fsu.edu